# Snake
A snake game clone for school project with difficulty settings, ranking board (hopefully)
Utilizing MVC Design Pattern and Java Swing

Folder: SnakeGame

Author: Group 2
Member: 
 - Nguyễn Hoàng Anh - 1652002
 - Lưu Phạm Mạnh Hà - 1752001
 - Nguyễn Thị Quỳnh Hoa - 1752017

## Alpha v1 1.0.0.1
No GUI implement yet
Only simple game board with snake object
* Done: 
 - Create Frame for main window
 - Create Panel for game board
 - Add Snake object that changes direction on key pressed
* To-do list:
 - More game object: Apples, Obstacles
 - Collision detected
 - Game information: score, highscore, timer
 - Logic layout for game